export const data = [
    {
      id: "0",
      question: "What is the first Pokémon in the Pokédex?",
      answer: "Balbasaur",
      variants: [`Mew`, `Balbasaur`, `Arceus`]
    },
    {
      id: "1",
      question: "Who are the starter Pokémon from the Kanto region?",
      answer: "Bulbasaur, charmander & Squirtle",
      variants: [`Bulbasaur, charmander & Squirtle`, `Bulbasaur, charmander & Cyndaquil`, `Bulbasaur, Pikachu & Cyndaquil`]
    },
    {
      id: "2",
      question:
        "How old is Ash?",
      answer: "10",
      variants: [`9`, `10`, `23`]
    },
  
    {
      id: "3",
      question: "Did Ash had deafeated champion Steven?",
      answer: "Yes",
      variants: [`No`, `Yes`, `It was a tie`]
    },
    {
      id: "4",
      question:
        " champion Diantha vs champion Lance , who will win? ",
      answer: "Diantha",
      variants: [`Lance`, `It will be tie`, `Diantha`]
    },
  
    {
      id: "5",
      question: "how old  is Iris ?",
      answer: "10",
      variants: [`13`, `10`, `20`]
    },
  
    {
      id: "6",
      question:
        "What is pikachu's type?",
      answer: "Electric",
      variants: [`Normal`, `Fire`, `Electric`]
    },
    {
      id: "7",
      question: "who is the boy kalos Serana have crush on? ",
      answer: "Ash",
      variants: [`Goh`, `Ash`, `Leon`]
    },
    {
      id: "8",
      question: "who is best rival of Ash?",
      answer: "both",
      variants: [`Leon`, `Gary`, `both`]
    },
    {
      id: "9",
      question: "Pichu evolve into which pokemon?",
      answer: "Pikachu",
      variants: [`Alolan Raichu`, `Raichu`, `Pikachu`]
    },
    {
      id: "10",
      question: "who is champion of alola region?",
      answer: "Name",
      variants: [`Ash `, `leon`, `Gladion`]
    },
]